Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Larry Kramer papers
1920-2015
YCAL MSS 722
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
200.30
(227 boxes) + 2 roll, 4 broadside folders, 2 record album storage
The collection documents the career of Larry Kramer as a playwright and author, an advocate for gay rights, and an activist in the fight against AIDS. The collection consists of writings, including manuscripts and drafts of plays, books, screenplays, and articles; AIDS-related material; diaries; correspondence; photographs; printed material; audiovisual material; and other papers. There is also substantial material relating to the founding of Gay Men's Health Crisis and the AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACT UP) in particular, and to the AIDS movement in general.
Kramer, Larry, 1935-
Conditions Governing Access
The bulk of the materials are open for research.
Boxes 49-50, 234-236: Restricted material. Contact the appropriate curator for further information.
Boxes 37, 58, 178-181, 202-205, 229 (electronic materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 29-30, 151-153, 189, 207, 228, 233 (audiovideo material) and 186 (reel to reel audiotapes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Larry Kramer, 2003-2016.
November 2016 Acquisition: purchased from Larry Kramer on the Donald Windham-Sandy Campbell Collection Endowment Fund.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into seven groupings: July 2003 Acquisition (Uncat MSS 520), July 2003 Acquisition (Uncat MSS 785), August 2007 Acquisition (Uncat MSS 975), and October 2008 Acquisition (Uncat MSS 1071), July 2011 Acquisition, February 2016 Acquisition, and November 2016 Acquisition.
Material within this collection has been organized by acquisition reflecting the fact that the collection has been acquired in increments over time.
Researchers should note that material within each acquisition overlaps with and/or relates to material found in other acquisitions. For instance, writings, correspondence, and material relating to AIDS activism can be found in most, if not all, of the groupings. In order to locate all relevant material within this collection, researchers will need to consult each acquisition described in the Collection Contents section.
Researchers should also note that similar material can be arranged differently in each acquisition, depending on how the material was organized when it was received by the library.
Larry Kramer (1935- )
Larry Kramer is an American playwright, author, public health advocate, and gay rights activist. He graduated from Yale University in 1957 with a B.A. in English, and is the author of several novels, including Faggots (1978), and plays, including The Normal Heart (1985) and Destiny of Me (1992), which explore themes related to gay life and the AIDS crisis. He has long been an outspoken advocate for gay rights and the fight against AIDS. He was a co-founder of the Gay Men's Health Crisis in the early 1980s, and later founded the AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACT UP) in 1987. Kramer is also the author of several motion picture screenplays, including an adaptation of Women in Love, for which he was nominated for an Academy Award in 1969. He is currently working on the manuscript of an historical work called The American People.
Scope and Contents
The collection documents the career of Larry Kramer as a playwright and author, an advocate for gay rights, and an activist in the fight against AIDS. The collection consists of writings, including manuscripts and drafts of plays, books, screenplays, and articles; AIDS-related material; diaries; correspondence; photographs; printed material; audiovisual material; and other papers. There is also substantial material relating to the founding of Gay Men's Health Crisis and the AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACT UP) in particular, and to the AIDS movement in general.
AIDS (Disease) -- Patients -- Drama; AIDS (Disease) -- Social aspects -- United States; AIDS activists -- United States; American drama -- 20th Century; American literature -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Dramatists, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Gay activists -- United States; Gay men -- United States -- Drama; Gay men -- United States -- Fiction; Audiocassettes; Born digital; Phonograph records; Photographs; Videocassettes; LGBTQ resource; Kramer, Larry, 1935-; ACT UP (Organization); Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc
- July 2003 Acquisition, 1968-2002; 33.38; (36 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Scope and Contents
  This portion of the collection consists of correspondence, writings, photographs, printed material, audiotapes, videotapes, and other papers by or relating to Larry Kramer.
  Arrangement
  Organized under six headings: AIDS Activism Files; Diaries; Writings; Family Papers; Audiovisual Material; Posters.
  General note
  Former Call Number: Uncat MSS 520
  - AIDS Activism Files
    Arranged chronologically.
    Files contain a wide range of material documenting the AIDS crisis and relating to Kramer's activism and advocacy in the fight against AIDS, including his work with Gay Men's Health Crisis and AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power. Material includes clippings, photocopies of articles, correspondence, medical reports, publications, conference programs, press material, newsletters, notes, and writings.
    - 1981-1983, 19 (Box 1)
    - 1983-1985, 18 (Box 2)
    - 1985-1987, 20 (Box 3)
    - 1987-1988, 20 (Box 4)
    - 1988-1989, 19 (Box 5)
    - 1989-1991, 17 (Box 6)
    - 1991-1992, 19 (Box 7)
    - 1992-1993, 19 (Box 8)
    - 1993-1994, 6 (Box 9)
    - 1994, 20 (Box 10)
    - 1995, 16 (Box 11)
    - 1995-1996, 14 (Box 12)
    - 1996-1997, 21 (Box 13)
    - 1997, 18 (Box 14)
    - 1997-1998, 20 (Box 15)
    - 1998-1999, 20 (Box 16)
    - 1999, 17 (Box 17)
    - 2001, 21 (Box 18)
    - 2001-2003, 19 (Box 19)
    - 2002-2003, 16 (Box 20)
  - Diaries
    - 1975, 16 (Box 21)
    - 1992-1999, undated, 6 (Box 22)
    - Mini diaries, 1977-1989; 13 (Box 22)
  - Writings
    - Women in Love (screenplay), 1968-1969; 9 (Box 23)
    - Women in Love and Other Dramatic Writings, 2002 (Box 24)
    - "Sissie's Scrapbook", 1973; 4 (Box 25)
    - "Four Friends", 1973-1974; 2 (Box 25)
    - The Normal Heart, early documentation, 1974-1983; 10 (Box 25)
    - Rubin Carter Hurricane, 1989-2000; 15 (Box 26)
    - Gore Vidal - Larry Kramer: the QW Interview, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, 1999; 6 (Box 27)
    - Faggots by Larry Kramer, Published version, (2 copies) (Box 27)
    - Women in Love by D.H. Lawrence, Published version, (4 copies) (Box 27)
      Includes a first edition and one or more copies annotated by Kramer.
  - Family Papers
    - "Memories of My Past" by Rea Kramer, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Scrapbook for Rea Kramer's 80th Birthday, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Audiovisual Material
    Conditions Governing Access
    Boxes 29-30 (Audiocassettes and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Audiocassettes, 1983-1998; (20 tapes)
      Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - ENNO, 1982 September 27; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889440)
      - J. Snuster / Bruce Anderson, 1988 January 27, March 3; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889457)
      - "Ideas" on AIDS - CBC Radio, 1988 June 6; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889465)
      - Project Inform, Update Town Meeting, "Nutrition", 1993 January 27; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889473)
      - Project Inform update: special report from the Immune Restoration Think Tank 2, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889481)
      - Gary Noble, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889499)
      - A. Bauer, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889507)
      - Larry Kramer, closing remarks at [Key West] Literary Seminar, San Carlos, Key West, FL, 1997 January 12; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889515)
      - New Haven Gay Town Meeting, WQUN AM, 1997 October 8; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889523)
      - Larry Kramer on WNYC (NPR), 1997 June 19; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889531)
        Annotation on the audicassette reads: "On the Line" hosted by Brian Lehver; subject "Sex + Sensibility" from The Advocate.
      - Dr. Robert Windom, 1987 May 19; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889549)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889556)
      - AIDS, "Awaken World", 1987; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889564)
      - "The AIDS Lament", 1987; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889572)
      - Advocacy and Literature, Dawidoff, Gomez, Kramer, Schulman, White, The Key West Literary Seminar - Tape 4, Part 1, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889580)
      - Advocacy and Literature, Dawidoff, Gomez, Kramer, Schulman, White, The Key West Literary Seminar - Tape 4, Part 2, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889598)
      - AIDS and Contemporary Theatre, A Conversation, Larry Kramer, Tony Kushner & Frank Rich, The Key West Literary Seminar - Tape 6, Part 1, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889606)
      - AIDS and Contemporary Theatre, A Conversation, Larry Kramer, Tony Kushner & Frank Rich, The Key West Literary Seminar - Tape 6, Part 2, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889614)
      - "Emprise", Tape 1, undated; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889622)
      - "The Emprise Opportunity", 1994; 1 (Box 29, Item barcode 39002104889630)
    - Videocassettes
      - "Shatzi is Dying: a video by Jean Carlomusto", 2000; YCALMSS722_0040; 1; 00:57:10 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002102338291)
      - Elton John: Live by Request 2:00, undated; YCALMSS722_0041; 1; 02:03:00; The audio is very low on the tape. (Box 30, Item barcode 39002102338309)
        There is a note attached from a Jed Mattes notepad. It reads: Larry dear - you rock!
      - Larry Kramer on NH Gay Town Meeting, 11pm news WTNH-TV 8, 1997 October 8; YCALMSS722_0042; 1; 00:05:44; The recording is in poor quality. Both the video and the audio are noisy. (Box 30, Item barcode 39002102338317)
        A note with the tape reads: Larry-As promised-Michael
      - "Condoms Don't Stop AIDS: Get the Facts that the Government Isn't Telling You", undated; YCALMSS722_0043; 1; 02:41:44; The condition of the video is extremely poor. Audio is also very low and there is a hiss throughout the tape. (Box 30, Item barcode 39002102338325)
      - New York Diary, a film by Jay Corcoran, 2002; YCALMSS722_0044; 1; 00:12:15 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002102338333)
      - Elton John: Live by Request 2:00 (duplicate copy?), undated; YCALMSS722_0045; 1; 02:00:52; This is a better copy of the Elton John concert special. (Box 30, Item barcode 39002102338341)
  - Visual Material
    - "Larry Kramer's Secret," poster, 1995 (Box 31 (Broadside))
  - Previously restricted material
    - Drafts and scripts of "The American People", 2002-2003; 17 folders (Box 32)
    - Drafts of "The American People", undated; 17 folders (Box 33)
    - Drafts of "The American People", undated; 17 folders (Box 34)
    - Drafts of "The American People", undated; 15 (Box 35)
    - Drafts of "The American People", undated; 13 folders (Box 36)
  - Restricted material
    - Compaq computer (Box 37)
      Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information. Disk # 2003.ycal.0728.0001
- July 2003 Acquisition, 1997-2001; 0.46; (2 boxes)
  This portion of the collection consists of correspondence, bookjackets and printed material, including Lambda book report, which were transferred back to the manuscript collection from the Printed Acquisitions unit of the Beinecke Library.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 785
  - "Keith" to Larry Kramer, letter, 1989 February 10 (Box 38)
  - Keith Condon to Larry Kramer, letter, 2001 April 17 (Box 38)
  - William Schwalbe business card, annotated (Box 38)
  - Time Out: New York, 2000 August (Box 38)
  - Atlantic Monthly Press, Winter, 2001 (Box 38)
  - The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review, Spring, 1997 (Box 38)
  - The Journal of NIH Research, 1993 July (Box 38)
  - Lambda Book Report, 2000 July/August (Box 38)
  - POZ, 1998 August (Box 38)
  - "Larry Kramer Two Plays - The Normal Heart and The Destiny of Me", book covers (Box 38)
  - "Larry Kramer - Faggots", book cover (Box 38)
  - The New Republic, 1998 April (Box 38)
  - The Village Voice, 1998 April (Box 39)
  - L G N Y: the Newspaper for Lesbian and Gay New York, 1997 July 6 (Box 39)
- August 2007 Acquistion, 1983-2005; 17.04; (19 boxes)
  This portion of the collection consists of correspondence, writings, Gay Men's Health Crisis files, notebooks, photographs, audio and visual recordings and other papers, which originated from Kramer's home in Connecticut.
  Organized into three series: I. Correspondence. II. Gay Men's Health Crisis. III. Other Papers.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 975
  - Correspondence
    Files consist largely of incoming and outgoing correspondence and email printouts, as well as assorted other papers.
    Files are arranged in very rough chronological order. When material arrived, it was loose and grouped into boxes by year, beginning with the year 2000 and ending with the year 2007. The material within each box was found to span a broader range of dates, and so date ranges are supplied in the list below to better reflect the actual contents.
    - 2000-2001, 18 (Box 40)
    - (includes earlier material from 1983-2001), 2001-2004; 15 (Box 41)
    - (includes earlier material from 1999-2003), 2004; 17 (Box 42)
    - 2004, 15 (Box 43)
    - (includes earlier material from 2003), 2004-2005; 13 (Box 44)
    - (includes earlier material from 2004), 2005-2007; 18 (Box 45)
    - 2007, 4 (Box 46)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985; 2 (Box 47)
    - Funding Proposal, undated (Box 47)
    - Publications, undated; 2 (Box 47)
    - Files, undated; 5 (Box 47)
    - ACT UP (early), circa 1983 (Box 47)
    - Files, undated; 3 (Box 47)
    - The Madison Project, circa 1993; 2 (Box 47)
    - The Madison Project, undated (Box 47)
    - Notebook - The Madison Project, circa 1993 (Box 47)
    - Notebook - The Madison Project, circa 1993; 2 (Box 48)
    - New York Blood Center, circa 1985; 3 (Box 48)
  - Other Papers
    - Lake Watch, 1996-1999; 3 (Box 48)
    - AIDS Clinical Research, 1996-1997 (Box 48)
    - Letters to Thomas Stoddard, 1990 (Box 48)
    - Photographs - The Destiny of Me, undated (Box 48)
    - "The Lady and the Hard Hat", 1973 (Box 48)
    - The Normal Heart, screenplay, 1986 (Box 48)
    - The Normal Heart, screenplay, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Magazines and various materials (Box 48)
    - David Scott Morgan photograph, circa 1990 (Box 48)
  - Previously restricted material, 1975-2005, undated
    Boxes 49-57: Restricted material. Contact the appropriate curator for further information.
    Box 58: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 16 folders (Box 51)
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 22 folders (Box 52)
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 18 folders (Box 53)
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 22 folders (Box 54)
      Restricted material. Contact the appropriate curator for further information.
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 24 folders (Box 55)
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 29 folders (Box 56)
    - "The American People" drafts, undated; 21 folders (Box 57)
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 100.38; (116 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  Organized into six series: I. Correspondence. II. Writings. III. Writing Files. IV. Professional Papers and Research Material. V. Personal and Other Papers. VI. Audiovisual Material.
  These series represent broad groupings. Material within one series overlaps with material found in other series.
  This portion of the collection consists of an extensive amount of drafts and manuscripts of and files relating to Larry Kramer's writings, including plays, screenplays, and books. Also found is correspondence, printed material, notes, and other files, stemming from Kramer's film work in the 1960s and 1970s, his AIDS advocacy and activism from the late 1970s to the present day, his AIDS-related research, and other professional activities. There are also some personal and family papers. This portion of the collection originated from Kramer's apartment in New York City.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1071
  - Correspondence, circa 1960-2008
    Organized into three groupings: Chronological, General, and Miscellaneous.
    Correspondence consists of incoming and outgoing letters.
    - Chronological
      This group of correspondence represents letters that were housed together in boxes according to year. The overall grouping by year has been maintained and the groupings have been arranged in rough chronological order, however letters within each grouping are not arranged in any order.
      - circa 1972-1982 circa 1972-1982, 19 (Box 59)
      - circa 1982-1983 circa 1982-1983, 14 (Box 60)
      - circa 1984-1985 circa 1984-1985, 15 (Box 61)
      - circa 1985 circa 1985, 15 (Box 62)
      - circa 1987-1988 circa 1987-1988, 14 (Box 63)
      - circa 1988-1994 circa 1988-1994, 14 (Box 64)
      - circa 1995-2008 circa 1995-2008, 22 (Box 65)
    - General
      Arranged alphabetically by correspondent or original folder heading, which appears in quotes.
      - Anderson, Gabriel, circa 1995 (Box 66)
      - Arkell, Rose and Tom, circa 1960-1968 (Box 66)
      - Averill, Brett, circa 1981 (Box 66)
      - Dramatist Guild, circa 1989-1991 (Box 66)
      - D'Urso, Joseph Paul, circa 1973 (Box 66)
      - Family correspondence, circa 1960s (Box 66)
      - Fan mail, circa 1970s; 3 (Box 66)
      - Gillespie, William, circa 1971-1974 (Box 66)
      - Kramer, Arthur, circa 1992 (Box 66)
      - Kramer, Larry, circa 1995; 3 (Box 66)
      - Kramer, Liza, circa 1978 (Box 66)
      - "Letters of Recommendation", circa 1995 (Box 66)
      - McFarlane, Roger, circa 1990s (Box 66)
      - "Mother's estate", circa 1996 (Box 66)
      - "The New York Times", circa 1980s (Box 66)
      - Newspaper articles, circa 1984-1987 (Box 66)
      - Prager, Robert, circa 1987-1990; 2 (Box 67)
      - Rainey, Fred, circa 1976-1978 (Box 67)
      - Umans, Richard, circa 1977-1985 (Box 67)
      - Writers Guild of America, circa 1990-1995 (Box 67)
      - Yale University, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-1980s; 9 (Box 67)
        Arranged in a very rough chronological order with original groupings left intact.
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s; 13 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s; 10 (Box 69)
        Includes two audiocassettes: "What's Going On?" by Paul Willcocks (circa 1985) and an unlabeled cassette (circa 1980s).
        Access to original audiocassettes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s; 12 (Box 70)
  - Writings, circa 1937-2005
    This series contains material relating to the creation of Kramer's writings and consists primarily of numerous copies of various drafts and manuscripts of his plays, screenplays, and books. For material relating more to the production, publication, and reception of Kramer's writings, see Writings Files.
    Organized into four groupings according to genre: Plays; Screenplays; Books; and Shorter Works and Other Writings.
    - Plays
      Arranged alphabetically by title of work.
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1991-1992; 19 (Box 71)
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1987-1993; 15 (Box 72)
        Includes early versions of The Destiny of Me, variously titled "Children Afraid of the Night" and "Furniture of Home".
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1987-1991; 14 (Box 73)
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1987-1990s; 15 (Box 74)
      - The Destiny of Me, rehearsal draft, circa 1992 (Box 75)
      - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, circa 1980s; 2 (Box 75)
      - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, circa 1986-1988; 14 (Box 76)
        Included are early versions of Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, titled "First Lady".
      - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, circa 1988; 14 (Box 77)
      - "A Minor Dark Age", circa 1970s; 2 (Box 77)
      - "A Minor Dark Age", circa 1976; 2 (Box 78)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 11 (Box 78)
        Includes drafts of screenplay based on the original The Normal Heart script.
      - The Normal Heart, circa1985-1995; 21 (Box 79)
        Includes some press clippings.
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 14 (Box 80)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1980s-1990s; 8 (Box 81)
        Includes press material, correspondence, royalty information and press clippings.
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984; 8 (Box 82)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1986-2005; 19 (Box 83)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1986-2005; 18 (Box 84)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1994; 17 (Box 85)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 12 (Box 86)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 4 (Box 87)
      - "Sissies' Scrapbook", circa 1974-1975; 13 (Box 87)
      - "Sissies' Scrapbook", circa 1973-1975; 16 (Box 88)
        Includes early versions of "Sissies' Scrapbook," titled "Four Friends."
    - Screenplays
      - "American Classic", circa 1970s; 12 (Box 89)
        Included are other versions of American Classic, titled "Sea Change".
      - "Hammerhead", circa 1966; 4 (Box 90)
      - "Hands Across the Sea", circa 1980s; 4 (Box 90)
      - "Head Games", circa 1969-1970s; 12 (Box 90)
        Included are other versions of Head Games, titled "Forbidden Colors."
      - "Head Games", circa 1970; 9 (Box 91)
      - "Helen and Harry", circa 1973; 3 (Box 91)
        Included are some written material, as well as magazines used for research.
      - "Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush", circa 1965-1967; 4 (Box 91)
      - "Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush", circa 1965-1967; 2 (Box 92)
      - "Just a Love Nest", circa 1970s; 6 (Box 92)
        Included are two printed items: Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs: A Tale From The Brothers Grimm, translated by Randall Jarrell and Walt Disney's Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs.
      - "Late Bloomers", circa 1980; 3 (Box 92)
      - "Lost Horizon", circa 1937-1972; 20 (Box 93)
        Includes a copy of the 1937 Robert Riskin screenplay of Lost Horizon, directed by Frank Capra.
      - "The Loudest Cry", circa 1961; 3 (Box 94)
      - "Misc notes/cards" (Box 94)
      - "Never Die Poor", circa 1969; 7 (Box 94)
      - "Passing Through", circa 1971 (Box 94)
      - "The Rich Get Richer", circa 1970s; 4 (Box 94)
      - "The Rich Get Richer", circa 1970s; 5 (Box 95)
      - "Robert Never Was" (Box 95)
      - "Stay Hungry", circa 1972-1973; 9 (Box 95)
      - Women in Love, circa 1967-1969; 15 (Box 96)
      - Women in Love, circa 1967-1969; 14 (Box 96)
      - "Unknown Script" (Box 96)
    - Books
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 17 (Box 97)
      - Faggots, circa 1975-1978; 17 (Box 98)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 15 (Box 99)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 17 (Box 100)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 13 (Box 101)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 15 (Box 102)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1994; 8 (Box 103)
      - Reports from the Holocaust, circa 1989-1995; 12 (Box 104)
      - The Tragedy of Today's Gays, circa 2004-2005; 2 (Box 104)
    - Shorter Works and Other Writings